https://lssnca.org/programs/youth-wellness/how-you-can-help/support-retreats.html

Become a Foster Parent
Sustain our "Be Well" Retreats and Child CampFor over 20 years, Youth Haven Camp has provided hope, guidance, and new beginnings for vulnerable children facing the unique challenge of being young and living with an HIV diagnosis. Although, HIV diagnoses have declined, DC still has one of the greatest needs for HIV support programs. In addition, we have found that our wellness education curriculum can be expanded to aid a broader population of youth, encouraging healthy decisions and positive relationships.
To meet growing demands, we need your help. Send a youth to our semi-annual BE WELL Retreat for $335 or help a child attend a week-long summer camp for $900. Any amount will sustain our ongoing efforts to help youth achieve their goals and be their best selves. During our camps and retreats, youth participants practice healthy habits for the mind and body, access peer support groups, develop leadership skills, and create life-long bonds.
$0.00
$6,030.00
65%
We have raised $3,896.00 of our goal.
Support our retreats and camps
owtlt5iau5rt
Donation Amount
(Required)
Full Name
First Name
Last Name
Email Address
(Required)
Address
Country
Address Line 1
City
State
Postal Code
Phone Number
Credit Card Information
Cardholder Name (Required)
Credit Card #
(Required)
Visa
MasterCard
American Express
Discover
Diners Club
Expiration Date (Required)
Security Code (Required)
Visa®, MasterCard®, Discover® & Diners Club® cardholdersYour security code is the 3-digit code at the end of the signature field on your card's back.
American Express® cardholdersYour security code is the 4-digit code located above the actual credit card number on your card's front.
Your total payment will be
4406 Georgia Avenue NW
Washington, DC 20011
Phone
(202) 723-3000
Fax
(202) 723-3303
Contact Us Today
501(c)3 Tax ID 53-0207407
© 2020 Lutheran Social Services of the National Capital Area
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
What Information Do We Collect?
When you visit our website you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and website use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our website.
Personal Information You Choose to Provide
We may request that you voluntarily supply us with personal information, including your email address, postal address, home or work telephone number and other personal information for such purposes as correspondence, placing an order, requesting an estimate, or participating in online surveys.
If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone.
Website Use Information
Similar to other websites, our site may utilize a standard technology called "cookies" (see explanation below, "What Are Cookies?") and web server logs to collect information about how our website is used. Information gathered through cookies and server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our website, and the sites visited just before and just after ours. This information is collected on an aggregate basis. None of this information is associated with you as an individual.
How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?
Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our business activities, providing service and support and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our website, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. The lists used to send you product and service offers are developed and managed under our traditional standards designed to safeguard the security and privacy of all personal information provided by our users. You may at any time to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers.
What Are Cookies?
Cookies are a feature of web browser software that allows web servers to recognize the computer used to access a website. Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored by a user's web browser on the user's hard drive. Cookies can remember what information a user accesses on one web page to simplify subsequent interactions with that website by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user's transactions on related web pages. This makes it easier for a user to move from web page to web page and to complete commercial transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online experience easier and more personalized.
How Do We Use Information Collected From Cookies?
We use website browser software tools such as cookies and web server logs to gather information about our website users' browsing activities, in order to constantly improve our website and better serve our users. This information assists us to design and arrange our web pages in the most user-friendly manner and to continually improve our website to better meet the needs of our users and prospective users.
Cookies help us collect important business and technical statistics. The information in the cookies lets us trace the paths followed by users to our website as they move from one page to another. Web server logs allow us to count how many people visit our website and evaluate our website's visitor capacity. We do not use these technologies to capture your individual email address or any personally identifying information about you.
Notice of New Services and Changes
Occasionally, we may use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our website, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. As a user of our website, you will be given the opportunity to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by clicking on a response box when you receive such an offer or by sending us an email request.
How Do We Secure Information Transmissions?
When you send confidential personal information to us on our website, a secure server software which we have licensed encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. The information is scrambled en route and decoded once it reaches our website.
Other email that you may send to us may not be secure unless we advise you that security measures will be in place prior to your transmitting the information. For that reason, we ask that you do not send confidential information such as Social Security, credit card, or account numbers to us through an unsecured email.
How Do We Protect Your Information?
Information Security -- We utilize encryption/security software to safeguard the confidentiality of personal information we collect from unauthorized access or disclosure and accidental loss, alteration or destruction.
Evaluation of Information Protection Practices -- Periodically, our operations and business practices are reviewed for compliance with organization policies and procedures governing the security, confidentiality and quality of our information.
Employee Access, Training and Expectations -- Our organization values, ethical standards, policies and practices are committed to the protection of user information. In general, our business practices limit employee access to confidential information, and limit the use and disclosure of such information to authorized persons, processes and transactions.
How Can You Access and Correct Your Information?
You may request access to all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in our database by emailing us using the contact form provided to you within the site structure of our website.
Do We Disclose Information to Outside Parties?
We may provide aggregate information about our customers, sales, website traffic patterns and related website information to our affiliates or reputable third parties, but this information will not include personally identifying data, except as otherwise provided in this privacy policy.
What About Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information?
We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words, when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection of our legal rights.
Permission to Use of Materials
The right to download and store or output the materials in our website is granted for the user's personal use only, and materials may not be reproduced in any edited form. Any other reproduction, transmission, performance, display or editing of these materials by any means mechanical or electronic without our express written permission is strictly prohibited. Users wishing to obtain permission to reprint or reproduce any materials appearing on this site may contact us directly.
Google Advertising Features
We have enabled Google Advertising Features on our website. By enabling Google Advertising Features, we enable Google Analytics to collect data about our website traffic via Google advertising cookies and identifiers, in addition to data collected through a standard Google Analytics implementation. We will not identify users or facilitate the merging of personally identifiable information with non-personally identifiable information collected through any Google advertising product or feature.
Enabling Google Advertising Features provides our agency access to demographics and interest categories of our visitors. We will use these analytic cookies and identifiers to develop more effective Google ads and webpages to better reach our target audience of community supporters and potential clients who are in need of our services. You can opt out of Google Advertising features for this site and others by visiting Google Analytics current opt-out features (https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).
LSSNCA uses Google Signals on its website, which for users who have activated Google Ads Personalization provides LSSNCA additional information from Google about users for the purposes of Remarketing with Google Analytics, Advertising Reporting Features, Demographics and Interests reports, and Cross Device reports. LSSNCA in turn provides similar information about its users who have activated Google Ads Personalization to the Google Signals network. Users can turn Ads Personalization on or off through Google's My Activity website.
Terms & Conditions
Terms & Conditions
Donation Refund Policy
We are grateful for your donation and support of our organization. If you have made an error in making your donation or change your mind about contributing to our organization please contact us.
Refunds are returned using the original method of payment. If you made your donation by credit card, your refund will be credited to that same credit card.
Automated Recurring Donation Cancellation
Ongoing support is important to enabling projects to continue their work, so we encourage donors to continue to contribute to projects over time. But if you must cancel your recurring donation, please notify us.
Powered by Firespring
